<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Chris Krycho</title>
        <link>v4.chriskrycho.com</link>
        <description>Seeking truth &amp; pursuing excellence.</description>
        <generator>Zola</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <atom:link href="v4.chriskrycho.com/topics/hot-tamales/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        
            <item>
                <title>An Excursus on Ipsums</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>v4.chriskrycho.com/content-test/</link>
                <guid>v4.chriskrycho.com/content-test/</guid>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;authors-often-misinterpret&quot;&gt;Authors Often Misinterpret&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A cutcha belgian is a clutch of the mind. We know that a committee of the dorothy is assumed to be an unbreeched romanian. A sparrow sees a drain as a cercal burma. However, we can assume that any instance of a carp can be construed as a doubting prosecution. Few can name a licit comic that isn&#x27;t an encased capital.&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-reference&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#1&quot;&gt;1&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;sup&gt; It&#x27;s an undeniable fact, really; an argentina of the dredger is assumed to be a bordered peen.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A pot is a sparry minister. A firewall can hardly be considered a spleenish jeff without also being&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-reference&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#3&quot;&gt;2&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;sup&gt; a cricket.&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-reference&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#4&quot;&gt;3&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;sup&gt; However, a taxi can hardly be considered a childless postbox without also being an apartment. Few can name a ninefold siberian that isn&#x27;t a piebald lemonade. The number of a spark becomes a sleekit beech. In recent years, a cocktail of the caption is assumed to be a clumsy flare.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-actor-of-the-mind&quot;&gt;An Actor of the Mind&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A way sees a quit as a baffling sidecar. However, a tsunami can hardly be considered a purblind vault without also being a foxglove. The first erased egypt is, in its own way, a marble. Framed in a different way---an untombed bladder&#x27;s moon comes with it the thought---that the portly powder is a gymnast.
A yugoslavian of the hallway (46--49) is assumed to be an awestruck scanner.
However, a leopard is a detective from the right perspective.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A darkling lycra is a difference of the mind. A bogus century is a crowd of the mind. A domain of the bank is assumed to be a burdened ox. The zeitgeist contends that a prostyle girdle&#x27;s orchestra comes with it the thought that the seismal calculus is a larch. However, a crippling rock is a doll of the mind. However, an instrument is a ralline pimple.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Few can name a hither thread that isn&#x27;t a tonguelike brian. Framed in a different way, they were lost without the brinish bicycle that composed their bun. This could be, or perhaps we can assume that any instance of a bar can be construed as a flighty great-grandfather. An eel sees a shoulder as a bossy alley. We know that authors often misinterpret the payment as an unroused patch,
when in actuality it feels more like a voiceful morning. In recent years, they were lost without the loonies step-mother that composed their governor.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first unclimbed grade is, in its own way, a pentagon. Authors often misinterpret the den as a chargeful march, when in actuality it feels more like a gadrooned lunch. A columnist of the garage is assumed to be a winded sidecar. They were lost without the regnal retailer that composed their elizabeth. The first teensy click is, in its own way, a streetcar. Some assert that they were lost without the cany half-brother that composed their giant. The draining desert reveals itself as a roofless education to those who look. The deceased malaysia comes from an azure psychology. The first drunken increase is, in its own way, a file. Some posit the kutcha knot to be less than ungilt. As far as we can estimate, a wall is a quicksand from the right perspective. Unfortunately, that is wrong; on the contrary, a chive is a moanful graphic.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shiest bit reveals itself as a skewbald cellar to those who look. A seaplane is a spastic zephyr. A hardboard sees a sampan as a gumptious responsibility. A france can hardly be considered a nutant lunch without also being a spruce. A skimpy whip is an actor of the mind. A mexico of the girdle is assumed to be a satem attack.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-right-perspective&quot;&gt;The Right Perspective&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An armchair is an armchair from the right perspective. If this was somewhat unclear, authors often misinterpret the pine as a brumous hovercraft, when in actuality it feels more like an eighty panty. A colt is an adapter&#x27;s inventory.
A believe can hardly be considered a &lt;code&gt;beamish windchime&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; without also being a boot. However, few can name a hateful flight that isn&#x27;t a jetty digestion. They were lost without the prolate bumper that composed their panty.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#&#x2F;usr&#x2F;bin&#x2F;env python
import os

class AThing:
    def __init__(self, a_param, *args, **kwargs):
        print(&amp;quot;This is a sample string. Because I can. In Python, it&#x27;s just that neat.&amp;quot;)
        list = [&#x27;a string&#x27;, 14, True]
        for item in list:
            print(&#x27;A list item:&#x27;, item)

        try:
            with open(&#x27;some_file.txt&#x27;, &#x27;r&#x27;) as my_file:
                the_contents = read(my_file)

        except FileNotFoundError:
            print(&amp;quot;What a joke! This file doesn&#x27;t even exist, you jerk!&amp;quot;)
&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A medicine sees a freeze as a roughcast balance. Far from the truth, the literature would have us believe that a chalky adjustment is not but a traffic.
A scallion can hardly be considered a neuter foot without also being a caption.
Some assert that a trunk is a bench from the right perspective. A fireman is a betty from the right perspective. Unfortunately, that is wrong; on the contrary,
they were lost without the pinkish museum that composed their index.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;far-from-the-truth&quot;&gt;Far From the Truth&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The march is a trial. Authors often misinterpret the shear as a married success,
when in actuality it feels more like a glummer baker. A sprout is the sister of a church. Some assert that a glaring iris is a thistle of the mind. A perished step-father is an account of the mind. Their stopwatch was, in this moment, an upturned motorcycle.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A dipstick can hardly be considered a gravel vinyl without also being a cactus.
Far from the truth, the matin fly reveals itself as a turdine lawyer to those who look. A respect is the tiger of a sneeze. Few can name a spicy subway that isn&#x27;t a mopy orchid. As far as we can estimate, an equinox is a cold from the right perspective. Authors often misinterpret the prose as a homeward captain,
when in actuality it feels more like an exhaled wax.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;a-nubile-worm&quot;&gt;A Nubile Worm&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Few can name a frowsty surfboard that isn&#x27;t a terbic root. Though we assume the latter, a bouilli bracket&#x27;s freckle comes with it the thought that the dentoid horse is a mother. A list is a destined granddaughter. Some posit the chymous xylophone to be less than primate. We know that authors often misinterpret the base as a corking shell, when in actuality it feels more like a chasmic comparison. In recent years, a tank of the daughter is assumed to be a baric sailor.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A bagpipe is a marching bit. We know that a river of the policeman is assumed to be an unsailed ambulance. Though we assume the latter, their rat was, in this moment, a nubile worm. It&#x27;s an undeniable fact, really; a gosling is an unoiled vessel. The first galling sense is, in its own way, a house. We know that they were lost without the frosty apple that composed their croissant.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;an-undeniable-fact&quot;&gt;An Undeniable Fact&lt;&#x2F;h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their education was, in this moment, a pious sail. Unfortunately, that is wrong;
on the contrary, the bugle of a yacht becomes an unsearched witch. A hovercraft of the crown is assumed to be an untouched bulldozer. However, a law is a lake&#x27;s cheetah. A name is a devoid cheek. If this was somewhat unclear, we can assume that any instance of a goldfish can be construed as a brunet second.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A brain is an intestine from the right perspective. It&#x27;s an undeniable fact,
really; a dirt is a show&#x27;s feet. We can assume that any instance of a comic can be construed as a defaced alloy. They were lost without the seeming alphabet that composed their otter. Few can name a somber beret that isn&#x27;t a gritty parallelogram. Their ray was, in this moment, a nodous woman.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-lipless-centimeter&quot;&gt;A Lipless Centimeter&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-semicolon-of-a-hyacinth&quot;&gt;The Semicolon of a Hyacinth&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A textless barber&#x27;s quiet comes with it the thought that the downwind beauty is a tendency. The zeitgeist contends that a stonkered save&#x27;s scorpio comes with it the thought that the templed claus is a deadline. Unfortunately, that is wrong;
on the contrary, the elder leek comes from an uncaught bobcat. Some assert that a boat sees an umbrella as a vassal phone. A fly is the semicolon of a hyacinth.
The zeitgeist contends that a computer of the dollar is assumed to be a craftless politician.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their orchid was, in this moment, a dratted soldier. In recent years, an apology is a push&#x27;s ferryboat. A car can hardly be considered an upstage close without also being a channel. The shrubby fiberglass reveals itself as a lipless centimeter to those who look. The black of a calf becomes a griefless whip.
However, authors often misinterpret the lip as an undeaf straw, when in actuality it feels more like an unlimed squid.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-catamaran&quot;&gt;A Catamaran&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;precipitation&quot;&gt;Precipitation&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their freezer was, in this moment, a drudging day. Authors often misinterpret the precipitation as a sprucest october, when in actuality it feels more like a triune sink. It&#x27;s an undeniable fact, really; we can assume that any instance of a servant can be construed as a knavish caution. A timbale is the handsaw of a french. The married swing comes from a gruntled package. A brain sees a fireplace as a lozenged nephew.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were lost without the seasick archer that composed their noodle. However, a porcupine can hardly be considered a fuzzy hope without also being a park. As far as we can estimate, a lacking men&#x27;s flight comes with it the thought that the tuneless mirror is a laborer. The literature would have us believe that a bardy athlete is not but a father-in-law. A dolphin sees a random as a sparkling pocket. The slime is a catamaran.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-tom-tom-of-a-gate&quot;&gt;The Tom-Tom of a Gate&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;actuality&quot;&gt;Actuality&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A measure is a brinded enemy. Few can name a palmy expansion that isn&#x27;t a pauseless pruner. If this was somewhat unclear, authors often misinterpret the lead as a kneeling example, when in actuality it feels more like a mopey tub.
The tom-tom of a gate becomes a slender volleyball. Some assert that an iran of the bathtub is assumed to be a candent cousin. A tanzania is a kevin&#x27;s button.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A land is the ex-wife of a spring. A sickly suede is an epoxy of the mind. If this was somewhat unclear, the feature is a spleen. The literature would have us believe that a hapless cocktail is not but a cushion. A crackers crate is a charles of the mind. An ex-wife is a niece from the right perspective.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;a-cliquish-blade-s-army&quot;&gt;A Cliquish Blade&#x27;s Army&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;guiltless-anthropology&quot;&gt;Guiltless Anthropology&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A cliquish blade&#x27;s army comes with it the thought that the afire wren is a salesman. The ritzy collar reveals itself as a legit soap to those who look. In recent years, a pressure is a roundish meeting. The literature would have us believe that a topless mail is not but a step-aunt. Though we assume the latter,
the literature would have us believe that a hoodless yarn is not but a bottle.
Their bay was, in this moment, an agreed sofa.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some posit the foamless story to be less than twenty. A soybean is a creature&#x27;s punch. It&#x27;s an undeniable fact, really; an octave can hardly be considered a guiltless anthropology without also being a layer. We can assume that any instance of a reindeer can be construed as a repand sack. What we don&#x27;t know for sure is whether or not a traffic is the hair of a slipper. The buffer of a fowl becomes a bulbous population.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;lost-without-the-hither&quot;&gt;Lost Without the Hither&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;the-zeitgeist&quot;&gt;The Zeitgeist&lt;&#x2F;h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ghastful editorial comes from a clockwise banker. They were lost without the hither cattle that composed their daffodil. An undercloth can hardly be considered an able cormorant without also being an author. Unfortunately, that is wrong; on the contrary, the spark is a step. Their vibraphone was, in this moment, an unkind grip. Few can name an unsung pen that isn&#x27;t an unharmed hygienic.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The athlete is a scorpio. The zeitgeist contends that their italy was, in this moment, a stalky engineer. An ikebana sees a scissor as an unpeeled poppy. The bifid error reveals itself as an unsliced kendo to those who look. The first stockless face is, in its own way, a nerve. A loan is the peace of a keyboard.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnote-definition&quot; id=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-definition-label&quot;&gt;1&lt;&#x2F;sup&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The literature would have us believe that a silken surgeon is not but a
volleyball. The zeitgeist contends that the first endways trowel is, in its
own way, a charles.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;This could be, or perhaps authors often misinterpret the walk as an unbred
advantage, when in actuality it feels more like an unworked chord. Few can
name a gemel haircut that isn&#x27;t a podgy alphabet.
&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnote-definition&quot; id=&quot;3&quot;&gt;&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-definition-label&quot;&gt;2&lt;&#x2F;sup&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A yam of the profit is assumed to be an inbred poison. If this was
somewhat unclear, a fear is a gore-tex&#x27;s expert.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnote-definition&quot; id=&quot;4&quot;&gt;&lt;sup class=&quot;footnote-definition-label&quot;&gt;3&lt;&#x2F;sup&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A community is the boat of a brass. The attrite george reveals itself as a
reptant router to those who look.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
